http://www.cartoonsupplies.com/content/privacy-policy

Shopping cart
There are no products in your shopping cart.0 ItemsTotal: $0.00
Request new password
Search this site:
Home
Privacy Policy
What information do you collect?
All information we collect is primarily in the interest of accurate order processing. When you sign up on our online store as a new customer, you will be asked to provide some personal information, such as first & last name, billing address, shipping address (es) and a contact e-mail address and telephone number. This information is used only for the purposes of processing and shipping your order, and will never be disclosed to any party outside of necessary channels to ship and process your order in a timely manner.
Is it safe to use my credit card online?
We take the security of your personal information very seriously. Our secured socket layer (ssl) uses the latest, industry-standard 256-bit encryption technology to ensure that your personal information (especially your name, address and credit card number) stays out of the wrong hands, and cannot be read or intercepted as it travels to our payment processing system.
Look for the https:// in the address bar of your browser when you checkout - the 's' stands for 'secure'. Our security certificate can be viewed by double-clicking the little padlock icon at the bottom of your browser window.
Disclosure to third parties
We will not disclose your contact details to any third parties.
© 2015 All Rights Reserved  | Conditions of Use  |  Privacy Policy  |  Shipping & Returns | A MyCommerce site
